2026, today, you need to shift away from role-based thinking to workflow-based
thinking. Let's say that you're like, I want to hire an editor.
But what we don't typically do is actually to find out on a more granular level,
what is this person actually responsible for?
Every single function in the business is just a series of actions when you take
it at the most granular level.
And most people just don't take the effort to really think through it.
So I'll give you like a wild example.
The first thing that like would begin would be an idea.
An idea is going to probably require some sort of trend research,
and then a ranking of things that are doing well.
That then moves to scripting. And as we go all the way along,
what we're end up making is one damn YouTube video.
And we need to break the entire business down into each of these kind of granular
levels.
And the reason that's important is because agents are doing each of these things.
Like I don't know if you've seen our media output is like tripled in the last
month and we haven't increased our head count at all.
And we did that because we have prompts that can do 30, 40, 50%.
They're eating up more and more of the workload so that one person can now do
the work of three and then it'll be the work of five and the work of 10.